Guide to the Stanford University, News and Publication Service, Notable Teachers Series Audiorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, News and Publication Service, Notable Teachers Series audiorecordings
1979-1984
SC1124
Stanford University. News and Publications Service
Stokes, Donald.
2.5 Linear feet 104 audiocassettes
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Arrangement note
The materials are arranged alphabetically by interviewee.
Access Terms
Audiotapes.; Interviews.; Stanford University--Administration.; Stanford University--Faculty.; Stanford University--History.; United States--Study and teaching.
Collection Contents
- Audiorecordings
  - Almond, Gabriel (Poli Sci), 1984 Jun 20; 103t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Arrow, Kenneth (Econ/OpRes), 1984 Mar 7; 95; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Atkin, Myron (Ed), 1983 Mar 16; 48; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Thomas A (His), 1982 Aug 11; 25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Baller, Adolph (Music), 1983 Jun 22; 67; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Banks, Peter M. (E.E.), 1984 Jan 11; 87; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Bates, Clayton (Engineering), 1983 May 18; 58; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Befu, Harumi, 1983 Feb 2; 51; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Beichman, Arnold (Hoover), 1984 Jan 25; 91; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Berg, Paul RE: Nobel Prize, 1980 Nov; 6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Berry, Stillman, 1981 Nov 4; 111; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Bienenstock, Arthur and Roslyn, 1984 May 9; 107a,b; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Blaustein, Julian (Comm), 1983 Jan 26; 46; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Bloch, Felix, 1982 Apr-May; 13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Boskin, Michael (Econ), 1982 Dec 8; 40; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Bowers, Kenneth (Psych), 1983 Dec 21; 86; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Brady, Richard, 1984 Sep 5; 118 (Box 1)
  - Buma, Maurine, 1984 Dec 12; 128; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Byer, Robert (engineering), 1983 May 4; 61; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Cannon, Robert, 1984 Feb 29; 94; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Carnchan, Bliss, 1984 Sep 5; 119; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Carrington, Joe, 1985 Jan 9; 131; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Chace, William, 1981 Nov 13; 14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Chaffee, Steven (ICR), 1982 Apr 2; 21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Collman, James P. (Chem), 1983 Mar 23; 47; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Corn, Wanda and Joe (Art), 1984 Jun 27; 110t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Craig, Gordon (His), 1982 Jun; 45; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - D'Andrea, Vincent (Cowell), 1983 Jul 13; 72; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Davis, Kingsley (Hoover), 1983 Jun 1; 66; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Decleve, Alain (Radiology), 1983 Nov 9; 81; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Diaconis, Persi (Statistics), 1983 Oct 5; 78; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Doerr, Harriet, 1984 Dec 5; 113; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Dornbusch, Sandy (Human Bio), 1983 Oct 8; 53; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Dorosin, David, 1982 Jan 20; 8a,b; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Drell, Sidney (SLAC), 1983 Jan?; 27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Earth Sciences Deans (Park, Jahns, Cox), 1982 Nov; 35; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Effron, Bradley (Stat), 1984 May 2; 104t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Everitt, Francis, 1984 Aug 22; 171a,b; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Enthoven, Alain C. (GSB), 1983 Oct 12; 79; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Finger, Thomas (parts 1 and 2), 1984 Nov 7, 1984 Nov 14; 126; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Falcon, Walter, 1984 Dec 5; 133; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Fuchs, Victor, 1984 Oct 31; 125a,b; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Gardner, John W. (Trustee), 1983 Jun 28; 71; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Glover, Frederic O. re: Sterling, 1979 May 24; 1a,b; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Goldstein, Paul (Law), 1982 Oct 13; 42; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Hall, Robert (Hoover), 1982 Nov 10; 43; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Hansch, Ted (physics), 1983 Apr 20; 59; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Hanson, Ronald (Engin), 1984 May 16; 106t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Harris, Stephen, 1982 Mar 4; 12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Hastorf, Al, 1984 Sep 19; 121; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Hellman, Bliss, 1984 Sep 19; 120; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Hilgard, Ernest R. (Psych), 1983 Dec 21; 86; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Hilgard, Josephine, 1984 Dec 19; 132; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Huggins, Robert, 1982 Jan 17; 9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Ireson, Grant, 1982 Mar 23; 20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Isaacs, Norman, 1982 May 6; 16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Jacobson, David S. re: Sterling, 1979 Aug?; 4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Jahns, Richard (Geo), 44; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Jameson, Michael (Classics), 1982 Jul 8; 24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Jedd, Joe (Bursar), 1984 Jun 13; 109t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kaplan, Leah, 1982 May 26; 15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kays, Bill, 1984 Sep 26, 1984 Oct 3; 122; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kennedy, David (History), 1983 Nov 2; 102; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kennedy, Jeanne (re: Queen's visit), 1983 Mar 9; 64; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kino, Gordon (E.E.), 1982 Aug 25; 34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kirkpatrick, Paul (Physics), 1983 Jul 27; 73; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Knuth, Donald (CompSci), 1984 Feb 1; 97; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Krasner, Stephen (poli sci), 1983 Mar 2; 54; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kreps, David M (GSB), 1982 Oct 7; 41; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Leavitt, Harold J. (GSB), 1981 Jun 30; 69; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Levinson, Henry S., 1982 Feb 17; 10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Long, Sharon (Bio Sci), 1984 Jan 11; 88; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Lu Valle, James (Chem), 1984 Jan 18; 90; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Macovski, Albert, 1982 Feb 18; 11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - MacKinnon, Robert (Music), 1982 Sep 22; 33a,b; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Mahood, Gail (Geology), 1983 Sep 14; 76; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Marshall, Hubert, 1984 Aug 8; 116; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Marwick, Arthur, 1984 Dec 12; 127; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Martinez, Alejandro, 1982 Mar 31; 17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Mayers, Jean (Engin/astro), 1983 Aug 24; 74; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - McBride, Tom (law), 1983 Feb 16; 52; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - McClenahan, James (Cowell), 1983 Sep 7; 75; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - McKinnon, Ronald, 112; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Meier, Charles (Econ), 1981 Dec; 36; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Merryman, John, 1984 Apr 15; 70; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Miller, Frank G., 1982 Jan 13; 7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Moser, Thomas (English), 1983 Sep 28; 77; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Mosher, Paul (Lib), 1984 Jun 6; 108t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Nagel, Gunther, 1984 Oct 17; 123; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Nix, William D. (Mat.Sci.), 1982 Jun 23; 23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Oliveira, Nathan (Art), 1983 Dec 14; 85; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Ortolano, Leonard (C.E.), 1982 Dec 8; 39; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Panofsky, Wolfgang (SLAC), 1984 Feb 8; 92; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Parker, Bruce (Pediatrics), 1984 May 30; 105t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Pearson, Darryl (Gen Sec), 1984 Mar 14; 96; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Pencavel, John (Econ), 1982 Oct 20; 37; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Polinsky, A. Mitchell, 1984 Nov 28; 130; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Powell, David, 1984 Jul 11; 114; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Preston, John, 1984 Jul 25; 115; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Raubitschek, Anthony (Classics), 1983 May 25; 63; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Raubitschek, Isabelle (Classics), 1983 May 25; 62; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Rebholtz, Ronald (Engl), 1982 Sep 8; 26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Rhinelander, Philip (Philos), 1984 Jan 18; 89; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Rice, Condoleezza (Poli Sci), 1983 Dec 7; 83; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Rice, Condoleezza (Poli Sci), 1983 Dec 7; 84; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Richter, Burton, 1984 Oct 24; 124; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Rick, John (Anthro), 1984 Apr 18; 100 t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Rosenberg, Nathan (Econ), 1984 Apr 4; 98 t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Ruotolo, Lucio (Engl.), 1983 Jan 4; 50; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Ryan, Lawrence (Humanities), undated; 101 t; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Schawlow, Arthur (Physics), 1983 Apr-Mar; 55; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Scheller, Richard H. (BioSci), 1984 Apr 11; 99; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Schimke, Robert (Bio), 1982 Sep 22; 32; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Schultze, Charles L. (GSB), 1983 Jun 8; 65; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Sheehan, James, 1982 Mar 31; 18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Shoven, John, 1982 Feb 12; 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Srinivasan, Venkataraman (GSB), 1982 Dec 15; 38; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1979 Jul; 5a-g; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Stockdale, James B. (Hoover), 1983 Nov; 49; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Swidler, Ann (Soc), 1983 May 11; 57; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Terman, Frederick E. re: Sterling, 1979 Jun 15; 2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Thompson, George A., 1984 Dec 12; 129; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Ullman, Jeffrey (Comp Sci), 1982 Sep 29; 31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Van Andel, Tjeerot (Geo), 1982 Oct 6; 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Van Dyke, Milton (Engin), 1982 Nov 17; 28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Vicenti, Walter, 22a, b; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Wald, Michael, 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Watt, Ian, 1983 Nov 30; 82; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Wellberg, David, 1984 Feb 22; 93; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Wesson, Robert, 1983 Oct 19; 80; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Wheelwright, Steven C., 56; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Williams, Howard R., 1983 April 27; 60; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Winbigler, H. Donald, 3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Wine, Jeffrey J., 1979 Jan 5; 68; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)